

HOSAM AL-REHANI

Full-stack web developer and unity developer

INFO:

ADDRESS:

Erbil, Bakhtiary

♦ MOBILE:

+964 751 149 0237

EMAIL:

Hosamre94@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO:

https://hosam.xyz

LINKEDIN:

@hosam-rehani-903609bb

SKILLS:

.Net Core	95%
MSSQL / MySQL / MongoDB	65%
JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS	95%
React	80%
Unity	95%
Photoshop, Illustrator, XD	95%
Web design	80%

OTHER SKILLS:

Git, Agile, WordPress, ARCore, ARKit, Vuforia, Grandnode, Nopcommerce, Bootstrap, Website hosting, UI/UX

LANGUAGES:

Arabic - Native Tongue. English – Read and Write.

PROFILE:

A passionate software engineer who worked on a variety of projects with a diversity of technologies and requirements, from ERP systems to task management solutions I have acquired a very broad experience about the software industry and especially the C# and JavaScript world. Usually, I work on the back-end side of a system, also when things coms to the front-end side I have great skills at designing beautiful websites while maintaining a very good UX. I am also interested in exploring the DevOps world and its ecosystem.

EDUCATION:

Syrian Virtual University:

Master of Web Science (MWS)

Syrian Virtual University:

Bachelor degree in Information Technology student.

Damascus University:

2013-2014

2019-now

2015-2018

Specialization Computer engineering -Technical Computer College.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Coders DC 2019-2020

Full stack web developer using .NET Core and MSSQL

Smart Gate 2017-2019

Full stack web developer using .NET Core and MSSQL

Joy Gates 2016-2017

Develop and publish games for android and IOS using unity.

Projects:

CoGile

Developed a task management system to help teams work together on multiple projects beside tracking their progress and achievements

CoGit

Developed a self-hosted Git server with .net core.

Roka accounting software

Developed and maintain accounting desktop application, build using winforms and MSSQL

Other projects, please visit my website at hosam.xyz